Sagemaker call:

Jupyter labs, has built-in python environments
Integrates with Git
Tensorflow/pytorch
To bring own: add to container and publish to Amazon ECR
Put data into S3 bucket for bult-in stuff
DeepAR for time series analsys on data
Use the Estimator function in python to utlize built-in Sagemaker functions
	-Just use train_instance_cout=1, no distrubuted training
	-
Can use for hyperparameter optimization
 	- Define objective matrix

*Stick with default size
*Create executionrole
*Don't mess with VPC
*JupyterLab has better UI
*use xgboost for regression, deepar for time series on msp
Just provide S3 bucket (change <bucket-name>)
Will be data SMEs, will do walkthrough on Friday evening
